http://www.canalholidays.co.uk/about-us/privacy-policy

Telephone +44 (0)1525 372355Email MenuHide navigationHomeCanal HolidaysCanal HolidaysPhoto GalleryVideo GalleryShort Break Canal HolidaysShort Break Canal Holidays3-4 Day Cruises3-4 Day Cruise MapLonger Canal HolidaysLonger Canal HolidaysGrand Union SouthGrand Union NorthNorth Oxford & Ashby CanalsFoxton & Market HarboroughSouth & LondonLeicester RingWarwick RingThames Circular CruiseBanburyLechladeOxfordStratford-upon-AvonEco-CredentialsCanal Holiday SafetyCanal Holiday Map (PDF)Skipper & CrewMaps & Guides For SaleNature & WildlifeHistory of the CanalsRecent NewsOur BoatsOur Boats2 Berth Narrowboats2-4 Berth Narrowboats4 Berth Narrowboats6 Berth Narrowboats7 Berth Narrowboats8 Berth NarrowboatsNarrowboat InventoryBunk Sizes & Headroom (PDF)PricesNarrowboat Holiday PricesWhat's Included?AvailabilityBookingSpecial OffersWaterside CottageWaterside CottageWaterside Cottage ImagesAvailability & Prices 2021 (PDF)Terms & ConditionsBooking Form (PDF)TestimonialsAbout UsAbout UsQuality Grading SchemeAccreditationsCustomer ReviewsGift VouchersBrochure RequestBoats for SaleNarrowboat BuildingRepairs & ServicingOcean Princess CruiseOcean Princess CruiseBrentford - NewhavenNewhaven - FalmouthFalmouth - Isles of Scilly - HomeTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyContact Us
Click here for latest updates about Coronavirus and your holiday.
Canal Holidays in the UKAll-Inclusive Prices (No Hidden Extras)28 Narrowboats from 2 to 8 berth for Weekly and Short Break Canal Holidays
Privacy Policy
The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd is committed to safeguarding your privacy online.
Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd.
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you.
The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd collects information on our web site via submission forms. We ask you to provide some personal information on these forms
2. What cookies are and how they are used.
A 'cookie' is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser. We use cookies that preserve your anonymity whilst allowing us to measure how users interact with this website. The cookies we use contain non-personally identifiable information and are stored on your web browser. You can manage your use of cookies through your browser's settings (for example, using Internet Explorer 9 select 'Internet Options' from the Settings menu, then click 'Privacy' and adjust the slider as required or click 'Advanced').
3. How your information is used.
The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd forms are used to process your bookings and brochure requests.
4. Who is collecting your information.
When you are asked for personal information on the The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd forms, you are sharing that information with the The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd only.
5. With whom your information may be shared.
Your information will NOT be shared with any third party. We have never shared it with anyone in 60 years.
6.. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we constantly update our system to protect your personal information, The Wyvern Shipping Company Ltd cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Canal Boat HireAvailability SearchHow many people in your party?2345678 (including infants)Starting between which dates?2021 Holiday DatesStart between 12th Mar – 18th Mar 2021Start between 19th Mar - 25th Mar 2021Start between 26th Mar – 1st Apr 2021Start between 2nd Apr - 8th Apr 2021Start between 9th Apr - 15th Apr 2021Start between 16th Apr – 22nd Apr 2021Start between 23rd Apr – 29th April 2021Start between 30th Apr - 6th May 2021Start between 7th May - 13th May 2021Start between 14th May – 20th May 2021Start between 21st May - 27th May 2021Start between 28th May - 3rd Jun 2021Start between 4th Jun - 10th Jun 2021Start between 11th Jun - 17th Jun 2021Start between 18th Jun - 24th Jun 2021Start between 25th Jun – 1st Jul 2021Start between 2nd Jul - 8th Jul 2021Start between 9th Jul - 15th Jul 2021Start between 16th Jul – 22nd Jul 2021Start between 23rd Jul – 29th Jul 2021Start between 30th Jul - 5th Aug 2021Start between 6th Aug - 12th Aug 2021Start between 13th Aug – 19th Aug 2021Start between 20th Aug - 26th Aug 2021Start between 27th Aug – 2nd Sep 2021Start between 3rd Sep - 9th Sep 2021Start between 10th Sep - 16th Sep 2021Start between 17th Sep - 23rd Sep 2021Start between 24th Sep – 30th Sep 2021Start between 1st Oct - 7th Oct 2021Start between 8th Oct - 14th Oct 2021Start between 15th Oct – 21st Oct 2021Start between 22nd Oct – 28th Oct 2021Start between 29th Oct - 4th Nov 2021Start between 5th Nov - 11th Nov 2021Start between 12th Nov – 18th Nov 2021Start between 19th Nov - 25th Nov 2021Start between 26th Nov – 2nd Dec 2021Start between 3rd Dec - 9th Dec 2021Start between 10th Dec - 16th Dec 2021Start between 17th Dec - 23rd Dec 2021Start between 24th Dec – 31st Dec 2021How long do you want to go for?Weekend BreakMidweek BreakFull WeekTwo WeeksShow All Available(Call us for other options)Do you have a preferred start day?I don't mindFridaySaturdayMondayTuesday (optional)Will you be bringing pets?I'm not bringing petsI am bringing petsI need a pet-free boat
Brochure RequestGoogle ReviewsBoat WiFi2 Berth Narrowboats2-4 Berth Narrowboats4 Berth Narrowboats6 Berth Narrowboats7 Berth Narrowboats8 Berth NarrowboatsTweets by @WyvernShipping HomeCanal HolidaysPhoto GalleryVideo GalleryShort Break Canal HolidaysLonger Canal HolidaysOur BoatsPricesAvailabilityBookingSpecial OffersWaterside CottageAbout Us Contact UsPrivacy PolicySite Map
Share this page on Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or LinkedIn,
Email to a Family Member or Friend,
Add this page to your Favourites, Print the page and more!
Simply click on a button below.
HomeCanal HolidaysPhoto GalleryVideo GalleryShort Break Canal HolidaysLonger Canal HolidaysOur BoatsPricesAvailabilityBookingSpecial OffersWaterside CottageAbout Us Contact UsPrivacy PolicySite MapBooking Office Opening HoursReserve a Boat Online 24 hours a day, 7 days a week using the Canal Boat Hire Availability Search above.Or please call us on +44 (0)1525 372355 during office hours:Monday to Friday: 9am-5:30pm.Also Saturdays from 1st April to 31st October: 9am-4pm.Tel: +44 (0)1525 372355. Email: Original Web Design by Services Online Ltd, Luton, Bedfordshire. Responsive Design by Robert Griffin. Hosting by WFA Support, Newport Pagnell, Buckinghamshire.Company Reg No: 00528254.The Wyvern Shipping Co. Ltd, Rothschild Road, Linslade, Leighton Buzzard, Bedfordshire, LU7 2TF, England, U.K.
